btc-i24.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy - BTC-i24 | Invest and wait 1 hour to get earned

The BTC Interest Group administration considers the Privacy policy aspect as its obligation to protect all of its' customers and their private information. Within frameworks of the Privacy policy, our customers are given the unconditional guarantee on non-disclosure of their personal information, transmitted to the service.  
When you as our customer use our services, we want you to be clear and confident as to how we’re using information and the different ways in which you can help to protect your privacy. 

**Privacy Policy  
Abstract**

We collect various information from our customers to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which type of account will suit your needs the most efficiently and profitably. 

We have tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you’re not familiar with terms like cookies, browsers, IP addresses, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to us here at BTC Interest Group, so whether you are new to BTC Interest Group. or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices and policies– and if you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact us. 

**Information we collect** We collect various information from our customers to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which type of account will suit your needs the most efficiently and profitably.

We have tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you’re not familiar with terms like cookies, browsers, IP addresses, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to us here at BTC Interest Group, so whether you are new to BTC Interest Group or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices and policies– and if you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact us.

The policy of the company as well as service agreement regulates the company's action on non-disclosure of private information of customers. Under private information of customers, we mean information specified during the account creation and its use:

  * Valid e-mail address
  * Birth date
  * Your Bitcoin wallet address

For enhance our security measures, system will generate login password automatically by random characters. Investors are responsible to record their login information and anybody who has the login information will identify as an account owner.

All these customer data are subject to said Privacy policy, this private data is not disclosed under any circumstances to third parties, except by a specific court order and are stored on a dedicated server, by BTC Interest Group. The information is stored in the encrypted form under AES 512-bit encryption algorithm.

Privacy policy is a priority for BTC Interest Group Ltd. in its communication with it's customers, and cannot be revised or amended. All aspects of the Privacy policy are adopted in the Charter of the company and authenticated by the signature of the Director of BTC Interest Group.

BTC Interest Group Ltd. uses this information solely for internal purposes to improve the quality of service and conduct operations that require the personal data of their customers for normal business transactions and daily operations. 

**** **** **** ****
